[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth", "Rock Hudson"], "LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "What was most important to Elizabeth, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJS", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Most important to Elizabeth were her family, her friends, her care about AIDS research, standing up before anyone that we knew of in Hollywood stood up after her friend Rock Hudson died a terrible death from AIDS.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Elizabeth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judy"]}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "NN", ":", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "I mean you've been a star the length of the time that she was, but there was something special about Liz Taylor, wasn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well, I remember when I first saw her, everybody wanted to look like -- well, not -- when I first saw her, when she did \"A Date with Judy' when she was about 15 and everybody -- all my friends, all of us at school, we all wanted to look like her.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Liz Taylor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "She was so giving and when she supported you -- if she liked you -- you had no better friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Did you love doing that play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Because that -- that -- that's top of the crop writing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ":", "IN", ":", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "AYLOR: Oh, wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "How did you like -- was Richard a helpful actor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ":", "VBD", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "He was a brilliant actor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Is that still the ring he gave you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, I don't throw it often --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Was this his engagement ring to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "No, it was like a couple of years later.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor"]}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "What made her that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP$", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Because of the -- first of all, Piers, you've never seen eyes like Elizabeth Taylor's.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "What was she like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Same as she was on camera.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "JJ", "VBP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ":", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 218, "question": "I think the world is going to miss Elizabeth Taylor, isn't it, Larry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "ING: Sure are, and even though she -- we didn't see much of her the last couple of years, she was very ill, we'll never have anyone -- think of it from --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor", "Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Did she really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Which I thought was incredibly sweet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What was the real Elizabeth like, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "And what did you think that your father ended up thinking about Elizabeth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "I know what he thought.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "What was your impression of her as an actress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, I mean she glowed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "What was it about her that enabled her to have that empathy, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, I think I always call it sort of rampant empathy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "How would you like the world to remember Elizabeth Taylor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "She was this incredibly vital -- and she had a great, great sense of humor.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Why are you afraid of the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Truth!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Now, I don't think it was a risk for her because she has had all the strength and the courage and the dedication to do what she was doing, that nobody could touch that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "What tangible effect did she have to improve people's live, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "POS", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "She had two effects.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Getting angry, Betty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "That was the way it was supposed to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Betty"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Dick, what's your favorite memory of Elizabeth Taylor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "My favorite memory is totally unlikely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "You know, Piers, there was just something so special about her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110326pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Do you feel like today we've really lost a generation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]